Guide to the New York Taxi Workers Alliance Records WAG.319
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series I: Campaigns, 1994-2010
  - Economic Justice: Response to Proposed Rulemaking, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Economic Justice: Scenarios, Jan 2004 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Economic Justice: City Council Outreach, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Economic Justice: Livable Income for Taxi Drivers, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Economic Justice: City Council Outreach, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Economic Justice: $5.15 is not Enough, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Economic Justice: Fare Raise: Recipts Before and After, May-Jul 2004 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Economic Justice: Fuel Prices, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Economic Justice: Some Facts and Figures, undated (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - General, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Campaign Priorities: Member Surveys, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Stop GPS: Flyers, circa 2004 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Stop GPS: Taxi and Limousine Commission (TLC) Focus Group Reports, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Stop GPS, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Stop GPS: Research, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Stop GPS: Research: GPS Uses, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Stop GPS: Omni, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Stop GPS: Contracts, Mar 2005 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Stop GPS: Taxi Technology Enhancements, Mar 2005 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Stop GPS: TLC, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Stop GPS: Driver Response, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Stop GPS, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Stop GPS: Fraud Allegations, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Stop GPS: Contracts, circa 2006 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Stop GPS: Driver Response, circa 2006 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Stop GPS: Taxi and Limousine Commission (TLC) Board Bios, May 2006 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Stop GPS, May-Jun 2006 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Stop GPS: City Council Advocacy, Jun-Jul 2006 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Stop GPS: Taxi Technology System, 2006-2007 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Stop GPS: Installation and Malfunctions, 2006-2007 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Stop GPS, 2006-2007 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Stop GPS: Strike Organizing, 2006-2007 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Stop GPS: Clippings, Feb-May 2007 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Stop GPS, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Stop GPS: Related Publications, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Stop GPS: Survey, circa 2007 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Stop GPS, Jun-Jul 2007 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Stop GPS, May 2007 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Stop GPS: Rulemaking, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Stop GPS: Equipment Agreement: Taxi Technology, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Stop GPS: Equipment Agreement: Digital Dispatch, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Stop GPS: Posters, circa 2007 (Box 13, Folder 3-5)
  - Stop GPS, 2007-2008 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Stop GPS: Incident Report: Maignam, Joseph, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Stop GPS: Litigation, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Stop GPS: Incident Reports, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Stop GPS and Fuel Surcharge, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Fuel Surcharge: Clippings, 2004-2005 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Fuel Surcharge: Call for Action, Sep 2005 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Fuel Surcharge: Workplan, Sep 2005 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Fuel Surcharge: Petitions, Sep 2005-May 2006 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Fuel Surcharge: Call for Action, Sep-Oct 2005 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Fuel Surcharge: Organizing, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Fuel Surcharge: Gasoline Price Research, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Fuel Surcharge: Media and Research, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Fuel Surcharge, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Fuel Surcharge, Jun 2006 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Fuel Surcharge: City Council Member Letters, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Fuel Surcharge: Taxi and Limousine Commission (TLC) Public Hearing, Jul 2008 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Fuel Surcharge: Petition, Jul 2008 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Fuel Surcharge and Intro 705: City Council Support Letters, Jul 2008 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Fuel Surcharge and Intro 705: City Council Member Letters, Jul 2008 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Fuel Surcharge, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Justice and Safety Rally, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Justice and Safety Rally, Dec 2005 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Democratize Taxi and Limousine Commission (TLC) Courts, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Democratize Taxi and Limousine Commission (TLC) Courts: Campaign Summary, circa 2006 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Democratize Taxi and Limousine Commission (TLC) Courts, 2007-2008 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Health Center: Research, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Health Center: Project Presentation, Apr 2006 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Health Center: Planning, 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Health: Needs Assessment Survey, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Health Rights for Taxi Drivers, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Health: Needs Assessment, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Health: Diabetes Research, Education, and Action for Minorities (DREAM) Project, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Health, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Safety: Ford Crown Victoria: Fuel Tank, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Taxis for All, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - General, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Safety, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Taxi of Tomorrow, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Cell Phone Rights: Neeru and the Heroes, Mar 2008 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Cell Phone Rights, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Justice for Zakir, Mar 2008 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Intro 705, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Intro 705: City Council Member Letters, May 2008 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Intro 705: Statement and Ammendment, 2008-2009 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Traffic Rights, 2008-2009 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Accessible Dispatch System, Nov 2008-Feb 2009 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - General: Workplans, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - General, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Taxi Driver Protection Act: Albany Action Day, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Taxi Driver Protection Act: Organizing, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Taxi Driver Protection Act: Motorcade, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Taxi Driver Protection Act, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - General (I), 2010 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - General (II), 2010 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Health: Driver Survey, undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Health: Driver Survey (Box 5)
  - Photo Album, 1998-2002 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Photos: Peace Rally and Queens Boulevard Office Demonstration, 1999-2002 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Photo Album: Peace Rally and Queens Boulevard Office Demonstration, 1999-2002 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Photos, 1999-2002 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Photo Album (I), 1999-2002 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Photo Album (II), 1999-2002 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Photo Album, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Photos, 2002-2008 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Negatives, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Photos: Justice for Shejadur, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Negatives, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Photos, 2006, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Photos, circa 2006 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Photos: Seattle, circa 2006 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Photos: Stop GPS and Philadelphia, circa 2009 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Photos: Stop GPS and Philadelphia (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Photos: Strikes and Accidents, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Photos (I), undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Photos (II), undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Series II: Legal, 1995-2010
  This series is arranged alphabetically by subject.
  This series primarily documents the internal activities of the NYTWA and one of the main services it provides to its members. It contains three types of legal documentation: advocacy cases for individual drivers, larger court, and legal research about topics including immigrant rights, traffic laws, and legal processes. The larger court cases were generally brought against the TLC as well as taxi garages and brokers. The research files attempt to navigate and understand the complicated rules and regulations placed on drivers from the Taxi and Limousine Commission (TLC), the Department of Motor Vehicles (DMV), and the city of New York.
  The advocacy cases represent much of the daily work of the NYTWA. Many members find out about and join the organization after seeking their legal help and advice. The office hours of the organization correspond with the schedule of drivers who experience a shift change around 5:00 am and 5:00 pm. Much of this time is spent speaking with drivers about appeals cases and fighting traffic tickets. These individual advocacy cases will be restricted until 2026 for privacy reasons.
  Access Restrictions
  Some material in Series II: Legal, relating to legal advocacy cases in support of individual members, have been redacted to ensure the privacy of these individuals. Names, addresses, phone numbers, hack numbers, and other information which might identify individuals have been blacked out. Names on folders have been replaced with numbers, in order to indicate distinct cases in support of individual members.
  - Hearing: Sohail Baig, Apr 9, 1998 (Box 13)
  - Hearing: Zahid Khan-Mohammed, undated (Box 13)
  - 501(C)(3), 2002 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Advocacy, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Advocacy (II), 2009 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Advocacy (III), 2009 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Advocacy, 2010 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Advocacy: Individual #1, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Advocacy: Individual #2, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Advocacy: Individual #3, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Advocacy: Individual #4, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Advocacy: Individual #5, Feb 2005 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Advocacy: Individual #6, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Advocacy: Individual #7, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Advocacy: Individual #8, Feb 2006 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Advocacy: Individual #9, 2010 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Advocacy: Case Lists, undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Advocacy: Individual #10, Mar 2006 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Advocacy: Individual #11, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Advocacy: Individual #12, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Advocacy: Crime Victims Compensation, 1998-2002 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Advocacy: Department of Motor Vehicles (DMV), 2008-2009 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Advocacy: Individual #13, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Advocacy: Individual #14, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Advocacy: Individual #15, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Advocacy: Individual #16, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Advocacy: Individual #17, 2005-2007 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Advocacy: Individual #18, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Advocacy: Individual #19, 2010 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Advocacy: Lawyers: Koehler and Isaacs, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Advocacy: Individual #20, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Advocacy: Individual #21, 2010 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Advocacy: Individual #22, 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Advocacy: Individual #23, circa 2009 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Advocacy: Individual #24, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Advocacy: Individual #25, Oct 2009 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Advocacy: Open Cases, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Advocacy: Individual #26, Nov 2009 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Advocacy: Individual #27: Family Visa Request, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Advocacy: Individual #28, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Advocacy: Individual #29, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Advocacy: Individual #30, 2010 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Advocacy: Individual #31, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Advocacy: Individual #32, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Advocacy: Individual #33, Nov 2009 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Advocacy: Individual #34, 2010 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Advocacy: Individual #35, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Article 8 Procedures, Jan-Feb 1998 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Blank Appeal Forms: Taxi and Limousine Commission, circa 2005 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Data Center, Aug 2002 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Medallion Agents, Oct 2002 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Department of Investigation, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Department of Motor Vehicles (DMV), 1999 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Department of Motor Vehicles (DMV), 2000 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Department of Motor Vehicles (DMV): Traffic Court, 1996-2000 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Fitzpatrick, Kevin: Notebook, circa 2000 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Freedom of Information Law (FOIL), 2010 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - General, 1998-2001 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - General, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - General, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Immigration, 1999-2005 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Immigration Rights, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Immigration: Health, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Immigration: Registration, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Labor Bureau: Contract Violation Cases, May 2000 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Licensing and Contracts, Nov-Dec 2005 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Metropolitan Taxicab Board of Trade (MTBOT), 2009 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - New York City Law, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Nnebe v Daus, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Notice of Opportunity to Comment: Rules of Conduct for Administrative Law Judges and Hearing Officers, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Omni Fairness Appeal, Jun 2006 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Operation Refusal, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Operation Refusal: Settlements, Apr-Jun 2004 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Overcharge: B. Taxi Management, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Owners Transport Communication: Radio Rights, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Parking Violation, 2007-2008 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Proposed Amendment to Rules Governing Taxicab Specifications, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Public Advocate for the City of New York, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Referrals, 2004-2005 (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Retainers: Koehler and Isaacs, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Referrals: Koehler and Isaacs, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Referrals: Koenigsberg, 2005-2006 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Research (I), 2001 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Research (II), 2001 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Resources, 1998-2001 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Rights, 1999, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Taxi and Limousine Commission (TLC): Appeals Pending, 2003-2005 (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - Taxi and Limousine Commission (TLC): Cases, Feb 2009 (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Taxi and Limousine Commission (TLC): Legal Presence Requirement, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - Taxi and Limousine Commission (TLC): Regulations on Taxicab Appearance: Memorandum, Sep 2003 (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - Tickets to Lawyers, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - Rights: Manuals and Training, 1997, 2003-2005 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Rights: Manuals and Training, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Rights: Small Claims Court, 1996, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Rights: Technology and Fuel, 2004-2006 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Worker Centers, 1995, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Series III: Administrative, Bulk, 1998-2010; 1972-2012
  This series is arranged alphabetically.
  This series represents the administrative work of the NYTWA and the industry research that does not directly relate to campaigns. The series is grouped in four major categories: clippings, financial documents, related organizations, and publications.
  The clippings are one of the only ways this collectiond documents the outcome of the NYTWA campaign and advocacy efforts. They contain many minor New York City newspaper such as the Queens Chronicle as well as now defunct newspapers such as the The New York Sun. The clippings also include print outs of online news agencies and blogs. They document the public attitude toward the taxi industry, the technology changes throughout the 2000s, and human interest stories about cab drivers. The clippings often come from publicatiosn geared toward specific ethnic groups, including India Daily and New India Times.
  The financial documents are all reating to grant funding from foundations. They contain applications, correspondence, and research that document the ways the NYTWA supported their staff and daily activities and new projects. The folders relating to organizations document outreach to related groups and project partnerships. Lasly, this series contains runs of publications relating to the industry. Of particular note the NYTWA’s own newsletter Shift Change. Other publications are produced by competing groups in the taxi industry, including the Taxi Insider newspaper, published by the fleet owner operated Committee for Taxi Safety.
  - Accessibility, May 2006 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Accessibility, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Awards, 2002-2008 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Awards: Purpose Prize, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Brokerage Corruption, 1997-2001 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Business Research, circa 2006 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Chicago Taxi Industry, circa 2010 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Clippings, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Clippings, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Clippings, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Clippings, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Clippings (I), 2000 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Clippings (II), 2000 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Clippings, 2000-2004 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Clippings (I), 2001 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Clippings (II), 2001 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Clippings, 2001-2006 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Clippings (I), 2002 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Clippings (II), 2002 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Clippings (I), 2003 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Clippings (II), 2003 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Clippings (III), 2003 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Clippings, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Clippings (I), 2005 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Clippings (II), 2005 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Clippings, 2005-2006 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Clippings, 2005-2007 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Clippings, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Clippings, Jan 2007 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Clippings, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Clippings (I), 2007 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Clippings (II), 2007 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Clippings (III), 2007 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, May 2007 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Clippings (I), Jun 2007 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Clippings (II), Jun 2007 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Clippings (I), 2008 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Clippings (II), 2008 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Clippings (III), 2008 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Clippings, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Clippings, undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Clippings: Bill Indauer for Bhairavi Desai, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Clippings: Collages, 2005-2006 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Congestion Pricing, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: Desai, Bhairavi, Mar 2003 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence: Port Authority, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence: Shift Change, May 2010 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Desai, Bhairavi: Notes, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Desai, Bhairavi: Interview (radio) (Box 13)
  - Desai, Bhairavi: Correspondence, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Desai, Bhairavi: Correspondence: A. Magazine, Jun 1999 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Desai: Talk on Organizing Non-Traditional Industries, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Distribution Materials: Driver Flyers, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Distribution Materials: Flyers, 1997-2000s (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Distribution Materials: Licensing and Health, circa 2008 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Distribution Materials: Member Packet, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Distribution Materials: Member Packet, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Distribution Materials: Member Packet, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Distribution Materials: Membership, circa 2004 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Distribution Materials: Press Packet, Dec 2001 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Driver Surveys, circa 2005 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Drug Testing Rules, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Dues Letters, circa 2002 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Employment of Unauthorized Immigrants, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Environment: Proposed Issuance of Additional Taxicab Medallions, Dec 2003 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Ergonomic Study, circa 2006 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Financial: Community Service Society, 2004-2005 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Financial: Foundation Information, circa 2001 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Financial: Foundations, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Financial: Joyce Mertz-Gilmore Foundation, 1998, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Financial: Nathan Cummings Foundation, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Financial: Needmor Fund, 1997-2000 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Financial: Needmor Fund, 2003-2005 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Financial: Needmor Fund, 2004-2008 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Financial: Needmor Fund, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Financial: Needmor Fund: New York Construction Workers United Application, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Financial: New Voices, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Financial: New World Foundation, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Financial: New York Community Trust Fund for New Citizens, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Financial: New York Community Trust Fund for New Citizens, 2007-2008 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Financial: New York Community Trust Fund for New Citizens, 2009 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Financial: New York Foundation, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Financial: New York Foundation, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Financial: New York Foundation, 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Financial: New York Foundation, 2002-2003 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Financial: New York Foundation, 2003-2004 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Financial: New York Foundation, 2006-2008 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Financial: New York Foundation: Technical Assistance Workshops and Services, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Financial: Norman Foundation, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Financial: North Star Fund, 1999-2002 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Financial: Open Society, 2000-2004 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Financial: Peace Development Fund, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Financial: Progressive Technology Project, 2002-2003 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Financial: Public Welfare Foundation, 1996-2005 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Financial: Resist, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Financial: Robin Hood Foundation, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Financial: Scherman Foundation, 2004-2006 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Financial: Sociological Initiatives Foundation, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Financial: Tides Foundation, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Financial: Unitarian Universalist, 2004-2006 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Financial: United Hospital Fund, 2004-2005 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Fitzpatrick, Kevin Michael: Memorial, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Funraising Law and Regulation, Oct 2000 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Garages, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - General, 2001-2008 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - General, 2005-2006 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - General, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - General, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Health, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Health: Safety Risks, 2005-2006 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Healthcare, circa 2008 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Immigrant Assistance, 2003-2004 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Immigrant Assistance: Legal, 2002-2004 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Immigrants, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Immigrant Rights, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Immigrant Rights, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Industry Analysis, 2002-2003 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Industry Research, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Insurance: Group Term Life Insurance Policy, Feb 2008 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Issuance of Additional Medallions, 2003-2004 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Labor Supply, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Leasing of Taxicabs to Drivers as Independent Contractors, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Mathew, Biju: Taxi! Cabs and Capitalism in New York City: Correspondence, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Materials for Luis Molina: Industry Research, 1998-2003 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Medallion Auction, Jun 2006 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Medallion Auction, circa 2001-2003 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Medallion Sales, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Media Guidebook, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Meeting Minutes, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Member Benefits: Insurance, 2001, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Member Benefits: Know Your Rights Manual Formats, 2006-2007 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Membership Forms, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - National Employment Law Project, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - New Voices Fellowship Program, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - New York City Council, 2005-2006 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - New York City Social Justice Fellowship, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Newsletter Writings, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Occupational Health Internship Program, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Office Equipment Contracts and Quotes, 2004-2006 (Box 10, Folder 18)